Playtime just got real.
Playdate is a action, comedy, family film directed by Luke Greenfield.
When out-of-work accountant Brian joins stay-at-home dad Jeff for a
playdate with their sons, he expects a laid-back afternoon.
Instead, they're chased by mercenaries, and Brian—totally
unprepared—must survive one absurd obstacle after another.
Brian, played by Kevin James.
Jeff, played by Alan Ritchson.
Emily, played by Sarah Chalke.
Leslie, played by Isla Fisher.
Simon Maddox, played by Alan Tudyk.
Gordon, played by Stephen Root.
Playdate is a 2025 American buddy action comedy film directed
by Luke Greenfield and written by Neil Goldman.
It stars Kevin James and Alan Ritchson alongside Sarah Chalke, Alan Tudyk, Benjamin
Pajak, Banks Pierce, Hiro Kanagawa, Stephen Root, and Isla Fisher.
The film follows Brian (James), a recently unemployed accountant and father who sets up a playdate with stay-at-home dad Jeff (Ritchson), with the two then
being targeted by mercenaries along with their sons (when Jeff reveals he and his “son” are on the run from both the military and the authorities).
The film was released on Amazon Prime Video on November 12, 2025,
where it became the number 1 film in the US that week.
The film explores themes of stay-at-home dad,
accountant, action comedy, clinical, cliché.
The tone is lighthearted.